Here are the pots and utensils we are going to need today.
We are going to need a sauté pan or a frying pan.
We are going to be cooking our chicken in here but not all the way through.
Later, after we sear it closed, we are going to put it on a baking sheet and finish it in the oven.
We are actually are going to be using two baking sheets today because one we are going to start off by cooking our bacon that will later go in with our potatoes.
We are going to be boiling our potatoes in here and that is why we will have this strainer.
We are going to let them cool, cut them and then we are going to mix them with our bacon and our Parmesan cheese.
We are going to be boiling our carrots and asparagus before we go ahead and roast them.
And I have another strainer here because we are going to be soaking our artichoke hearts in lemon juice.
So we are going to put our artichoke hearts in here and we are going to squeeze our lemon right over the top.
We are to be using this to keep the seeds out of here.
We are going to be roasting our vegetables in this pan.
We are going to be using another one of these little containers in that we are going to make our butter and put that in to the freezer.
We are using three bowls here. We are going to be putting flour in one, bread crumbs in another and then making an egg wash. We are going to be needing a knife, a spoon, a peeler, some measuring spoons, cutting board and because we are using chicken, we are going to be using these gloves.